-I'm ready. -You sure?
-我準備好了 -你確定？
Let me just straighten out your helmet there.
讓我幫你把頭盔戴好
-Thanks, Daddy. -No, no. One daddy, two mommies.
-謝謝你，爸爸 -不，一個爸爸，二個媽媽
-All right, it's all yours. -Okay, okay.
-好了，你去吧 -沒問題
There you go, there you go.
加油
Wow, Ben's first big kid's bike. This is so exciting!
這是班第一次騎腳踏車 我真的是好興奮
Oh, yeah, I remember mine.
對，我還記得我的第一次
It was my sixth birthday. I went to the park...
那是我六歲的生日 我到公園去…
-and I got on it and it bent. -Yeah.
-坐上腳踏車，它就垮了 -沒錯
-I never had a bike of my own. -What?
-我從來沒有屬於自己的腳踏車 -什麼？
We didn't have a lot of money.
我們家很窮
But the girl across the street had the best bike.
但住在對街的女孩 有一輛最酷的腳踏車
It was pink and it had rainbow-colored tassels hanging off the handles...
它是粉紅色的 把手掛著五顏六色的流蘇…
and a bell and this big, white wicker basket...
還有鈴鐺 一個白色的大籃子…
with those plastic daisies stuck on.
上面黏著塑膠做的小雛菊
That sounds like my first bike.
聽起來很像是我的第一輛腳踏車
My dad gave me his old one.
我爸把他以前的腳踏車送給我
-Did the girl ever let you ride it? -No.
-那個女孩讓你騎它嗎？ -不
But she gave me the box that it came in.
但她把裝腳踏車的紙箱送給我
It had a picture of the bike on the front.
紙箱前面印了腳踏車的圖案
So I would sit on it and my stepdad would drag me around the backyard.
我可以坐在上面 我繼父會拖著我在後院跑
That is so unfair.
那真的太不公平了
Not really, I got to drag him around too.
也不能那麼說 我也會拖著他跑
The One With All the Candy
本集播出：糖果皇后
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey, what are you guys doing?
你們在做什麼？
Making candy for the neighbors.
我在為鄰居做糖果
I'm sorry, who?
對不起，你說誰？
I'm gonna hang a basket on the door.
我要在門上掛一個籃子
When the neighbors walk by,  they can take a piece.
只要鄰居一走過去 他們就可以拿一塊糖果
-But we don't know the neighbors. -I do.
-但我們不認識我們的鄰居 -我認識
There's, let's see,  the guy with the mustache...
讓我想一想 那個留鬍子的男人…
smokes-a-lot lady,  some kids I've seen...
老煙槍婆婆 我看過一些孩子…
and the red-haired guy who does not like to be called Rusty.
還有紅頭髮的男人 他不喜歡別人叫他小紅
See, this is exactly why I'm making this candy.
看吧，這就是 我要做糖果的原因
We can get to know our neighbors.
我們可以認識鄰居
Wouldn't it be easier if we just moved?
搬家應該會比較簡單一點吧？
Good morning!
早安
-Somebody's in a good mood. -Well, why shouldn't I be?
-有人心情不錯 -我為什麼要心情不好？
I have great friends. I have a wonderful job..
我有很棒的朋友 有很棒的工作…
Where you can make out with your assistant.
而且可以在辦公室跟助理鬼混
It's not a big deal.
那沒有什麼大不了的
We stayed up creating a plan so that us dating won't be a problem.
我們整晚沒睡在想計劃 確保我們的交往不會有問題
Oh, yeah? What's the plan?
是嗎？你們想出什麼計劃？
We.. We are not...
我們…我們不會…
going to let it...
讓它…
be a problem.
變成問題
It took you all night to come up with that plan?
你們花了一整晚 想出那個計劃？
Well, you know,  we did other stuff too.
你知道的 我們還做了別的事
Did you two...?
你們兩個…
Oh, I don't sleep with guys on the first date.
喔，我不會在第一次約會時 就跟男伴上床
-Matt Wire, Mark Lynn, Ben Wise.. -Anymore!
-麥特威爾，馬克林恩，班韋斯… -我已經不會了
Hi, Tag, I have a conference call today, is that correct?
泰格，今天我要開會 對吧？
-Yes, at 4. -Okay, thank you, that'll be all.
-沒錯，四點開會 -謝謝你，沒事了
Wait, wait.
等一下
Did you see that?
你看到了嗎？
He had no idea there was something going on between us.
他沒發現 我們在戀愛
-I'd better get back to my desk. -Okay, hard worker.
-我得回去工作了 -好吧，工作狂
I'll put that in your evaluation.
我會在你的評估表裡提到那一點
-My what? -You've been here for two months now.
-我的什麼？ -你已經來上班兩個月了
And your boss is required to hand in a performance evaluation.
你的上司必須為你的表現做評估
But you know, there is one thing that I have yet to evaluate.
但有一件事 我還沒有做評估
-Are you serious? -No, but I've always wanted to do that.
-你是認真的嗎？ -不，我一直都想那麼做
Can you help me clean this up?
你可以幫我把東西撿起來嗎？
The basket is totally empty! The neighbors ate it all!
籃子是空的 鄰居們把糖果吃掉了
Well, either that or...
喔，不然的話就是…
Joey!
喬伊
Yeah?
-Did you eat all the neighbor candy? -That was the plan.
-你吃掉給鄰居們的糖果了嗎？ -本來我打算要那麼做
When I got to it,  there was only a few pieces left.
我走到籃子邊時 裡面只剩幾塊糖果
They've come by all day. They love it.
整天人潮川流不息 他們喜歡它
They love my candy?
他們喜歡我的糖果？
-Oh, man, I gotta go make more. -Hey, Mon.
-天啊，我得多做一點 -嘿，摩妮卡
Make some more lasagna too. Something might have happened to a chunk of it.
多做一點千層面 或許它也會很受歡迎
Ross, the neighbors ate all my candy.
羅斯，鄰居們吃光了我的糖果
Mine stole my newspaper.
我的鄰居偷走我的報紙
It's like a crime wave.
這簡直是犯罪潮
Phoebe, you got a second?
菲比，你有空嗎？
Sure.
當然有
Ever since you told me about that bike...
自從你告訴我 那個腳踏車的故事…
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
它一直在我腦中揮之不去
I mean, everyone should have a first bike, you know? So...
我是說大家都該有第一輛腳踏車 你知道嗎？所以…
Oh, my God, Ross!
我的天啊，羅斯
-You like it? -I love it!
-你喜歡嗎？ -我愛死它了
-Yeah? -Oh, oh, God..
-是嗎？ -喔，天啊…
And I love you.
我愛你
Not that way.
不是那一種愛
But the bike got you a lot closer.
但這輛腳踏車讓你跟我更親近了
Well, take it downstairs.
喔，把它牽到樓下去
You know, give it a test drive.
試騎一下
Okay. Oh, my God.
好的，我的天啊
My first bike!
我的第一輛腳踏車
Thank you for the best present I've ever gotten.
謝謝你 這是我收過最棒的禮物
You're welcome.
別客氣
Oh, and Chandler's about to cry.
錢德快哭了
Am not.
我才沒有
Who is that?
是誰？
Don't worry, I'm brave.
別擔心，我很勇敢
I.. I am brave.
我…我很勇敢
No, no, no, no!
不
Can you tell me who is there, please?
請問你是誰？
My name's Gary. I live upstairs.
我是蓋瑞，我住在樓上
-Hi. -Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
-Do you know what time it is? -It's candy time.
-你知道現在幾點了嗎？ -現在是糖果時間
My roommate says they taste like little drops of heaven.
我室友說它們吃起來 就像是天上掉下來的禮物
Oh, please.
喔，拜託
Did you hear that? "Little drops of heaven."
你聽到了嗎？ 「天上掉下來的禮物」
Four a.m.
凌晨四點
So can I get some candy?
你能給我一點糖果嗎？
I am sorry, but some of us have to get up early and go to work.
對不起，但我們之中有人 還得早起去上班
He does not know that I am not "some of us."
他不知道我不是「那個人」
I'm sorry, but I'll put some out in the morning.
對不起 但明天一大早我會做一些糖果
Okay, I'll swing by later.
好吧，我待會再來
You live in this building?
你住在這裡？
Seems like I'd remember you.
我應該會記得你
Night, Gar.
晚安，蓋瑞
So did you read your evaluation yet?
你看了你的評估表嗎？
No, it was marked "confidential."
不，上面寫了「極機密」
I just sent it to human resources.
我剛剛把它送到人事處了
Please, you're kidding, right? I wrote that one as a joke for you.
拜託，你是在開玩笑，對吧？ 我故意寫那份評估表來跟你開玩笑
A joke they would appreciate?
他們會喜歡這個玩笑嗎？
I'm thinking, no.
我想不會
-What did you say? -I said you were a good kisser...
-你寫了什麼？ -我說你是接吻高手…
and that I liked your teeny, tiny tushy.
我喜歡你又小又挺的屁股
No, not my tushy.
不，你不該那麼說
It gets worse.
還有更糟糕的事
About your initiative, I wrote:
關於你的主動性，我說：
"He was able to unhook my bra with minimal supervision."
「他幾乎不需要指導 就能解開我的胸罩」
Under problems with performance,  I wrote, "Dear God, I hope not."
至於你的表現會不會有問題 我說：「天啊，希望不要有」
And then.. And then I drew a little smiley face.
然後…然後我劃了 一個微笑的小臉
And then a small pornographic sketch.
還有一張色情小素描
That is so sweet of you to get Phoebe that bike.
你送菲比腳踏車 真的太貼心了
When I heard the story, I almost cried.
我聽到那個故事時 差點就哭了
Almost cried, huh?
你差點哭了？
Hear that, Chandler? "Almost" cried.
你聽到了嗎？錢德，「差點」哭了
Hey, you cry every time somebody talks about Titanic.
只要有人提到《鐵達尼克號》 你每次都會哭
Those two had only each other.
他們兩個只有彼此
She really likes it, huh?
她真的很喜歡它吧？
Oh, yeah. I saw her walking it down the street.
對，我看到她牽著它過街
She had these flowers in the basket. It was so cute.
她的籃子裡面還有花 那真的很可愛
I saw her this morning, walking it by the park.
今天早上我看到她 牽著它在公園散步
Wait, she was walking the bike?
等一下，她牽著腳踏車？
Both times?
兩次都是？
-Hey, Phoebe. -Oh, hi!
-嗨，菲比 -嗨
-Hey, so you enjoying the bike? -Oh, uh-huh, so much.
-你喜歡你的腳踏車嗎？ -非常喜歡
Phoebe, you do know how to ride a bike, don't you?
菲比，你會騎腳踏車吧？
Of course.
當然
Can we see you ride it?
我們能看你騎腳踏車嗎？
Okay.
好吧
See?
你們看到了嗎？
I told you not to get involved with your assistant.
我早就跟你說 不要跟助理交往
There's no such thing as a secret when it comes to affairs.
只要是地下情 絕對是紙包不住火的
Did you hear that, Chandler?
你聽到了嗎？錢德
No such thing.
紙是包不住火的
What happened? I'm just eating candy.
發生了什麼事？我只是在吃糖果
Maybe it's not that bad. They might not take it the way I meant it.
或許沒有那麼糟糕 他們可能看不懂我的意思
Absolutely, you know? Because "tushy" can mean both ass...
當然囉，你知道嗎？ 因為「小屁屁」可以指屁股…
and good worker.
跟好員工
I just gotta get the thing back.
我得把評估表拿回來
Rach? That sketch you mentioned?
瑞秋，還記得你提到的素描嗎？
Might it have looked a little like this?
它跟這幅素描很像嗎？
Oh, my God, Joey!
我的天啊，喬伊
-What is the matter with you? -God!
-你是怎麼了？ -天啊
This little talent came in handy before I could afford porn.
在我買不起色情雜誌前 這點天份還蠻有用的
Hi, I'm sorry. I know it's after hours, but I really need candy.
嗨，對不起，我知道現在是 休息時間，但我真的需要糖果
I'm sorry, I can't help you. See? Rules are rules.
對不起，我幫不了你 看到了沒？規定就是規定
Please, I have people coming from out of town today.
拜託，我住在外地的朋友 今天來看我
-I told them all about your candy. -You're kidding.
-我跟他們提起你的糖果 -你是在開玩笑
Out-of-towners, huh? What did you tell them?
他們是外地來的？ 你怎麼跟他們說的？
I told them your candy was absolutely indescribable.
我告訴他們你的糖果 真的是好吃到無法形容
Some people have said it's "little drops of heaven." But whatever.
有人說它是「天上 掉下來的禮物」，但那不重要
-Please, can't you help me out? -Hey, Chandler, do we know that lady?
-拜託，你不能幫幫我嗎？ -錢德，我們認識那位女士嗎？
Isn't she the woman who lives below you and has sex really loud?
她不是住在你樓下 做愛時會大叫的那個女人嗎？
All right, I'll do it just this once.
好吧，我只破例一次
-But you can't tell anyone. -Please, just give it to me.
-但你不能告訴任何人 -求求你，快給我吧
Yeah, that's her.
對，就是她
-Thank you. -Unbelievable!
-謝謝你 -不可思議
I can't believe that sign didn't work.
我不敢相信紙條沒有用
You know what would work? Stop making candy.
你知道什麼才會有用嗎？ 別再做糖果了
But they like it.
但他們喜歡它
You mean they like you.
你是說他們喜歡你
Maybe.
或許吧
Is that why you became a chef,  so people would like you?
那就是你當廚師的原因？ 你要大家喜歡你？
You want to talk about getting people to like you, huh, funny man?
你要跟我談怎麼讓別人 喜歡你嗎？小丑
Just remember everything I taught you and you'll be fine.
記住我教你的一切 你會沒事的
Okay? Here we go.
好嗎？開始吧
Ready, set..
就位，預備…
Wait, this seat is really uncomfortable.
等一下，這個椅子 真的很不舒服
Maybe before we start we should just get another one.
或許我們得換張椅子 再來練習
Perhaps like an airplane seat, or a beanbag chair!
或許我們該換個飛機座椅 或懶骨頭
You can't get out of this. You have to learn how to ride a bike.
你不能逃避這件事 你得學會騎腳踏車
Why? Why do I have to learn?
為什麼我非學不可？
-Well, in case of an emergency. -What kind of emergency?
-以防發生緊急事故 -什麼樣的緊急事故？
Well, what if a man comes along and puts a gun to your head and says:
如果有人走過來 拿槍抵著你的頭說：
"You ride this bike or I'll..
快騎上腳踏車，不然我會…
I'll shoot you."
我會開槍打你
I would ring the bell to distract him.
我會按鈴鐺分散他的注意力
Then I would knock the gun away with a Chinese throwing star.
然後我會用中國的飛鏢 把那個傢伙敲昏
Okay, Phoebe, just get on the bike...
好吧，菲比，快坐上腳踏車…
and, hey, I'll hold you up and push you. Okay?
我會扶著你幫你推，好嗎？
You won't let go?
你不會放手？
-No. -You swear?
-我不會 -你發誓
I swear.
我發誓
-Okay. -Come on.
-好吧 -來吧
Here we go. All right?
好了，要開始了，好嗎？
All right?
-好吧 -好嗎？
Feel good? All right, try pedaling.
感覺不錯吧？ 好了，試著踩踏板
That's it, you're doing great. Yes, take control.
對了，你做的很好 對，控制住車子
Yes, yes, yes!
這就對了
Oh, no!
喔，不
You swore!
你發過誓的
-I just thought you were doing so well. -I am shocked. Shocked!
-我認為你騎得很好 -我真的很震驚
It's a legitimate learning technique.
大家都是那樣子學腳踏車的
Wow.
哇
Hey, there's some people outside asking about candy.
嘿，外面有些人在問糖果的事
They'll just have to wait, okay? I only got two hands!
他們得等，好嗎？ 我只有兩隻手
-Need some help? -No, you don't know the system.
-需要我幫忙嗎？ -不，你不熟悉流程
I don't need nobody messing with the system!
我不希望任何人破壞我的流程
By the way, the week before your wedding, you may not see a lot of me.
還有，你結婚前一個星期 不會常常看到我
Oh, hello, liar.
嗨，騙子
Look, I'm really sorry I let go of the bike.
聽著，我真的很抱歉 放開了你的腳踏車
I could've been killed, you know.
我可能會沒命的
I know, I know.
我知道
But can we please try it again?
但你能再試一次嗎？
I mean, you were so close, Phoebe.
我是說你只差一點就成功了，菲比
Well, I would love to...
喔，我很樂意…
but the bike got stolen and the police have no suspects.
但腳踏車被偷了 警察找不到嫌犯
-Phoebe. -What?
-菲比 -什麼？
What the hell?
怎麼會這樣？
You know what?
你知道嗎？
If you won't learn how to ride,  then I'm sorry...
如果你不學騎腳踏車 那麼我很抱歉…
-I have to take it back. -But why?
-我得把它收回去 -什麼？為什麼？
Because it's...
因為它…
It'd be like you having this guitar...
它就像你買了這把吉他…
and never playing it.
卻從來不彈它
Okay, this guitar wants to be played.
好吧，這把吉他希望被彈
And this bike wants to be ridden.
這輛腳踏車希望被騎
And if you don't ride it...
如果你不騎它…
you're killing its spirit.
你就是在扼殺它的靈魂
The bike...
腳踏車…
is dying.
快死了
All right. If you care enough to make up that load of crap, okay.
好吧，如果你真的那麼在乎 不惜撒下漫天大謊，我學就是了
Great.
太棒了
You're making the bike very happy.
你讓腳踏車非常快樂
Okay, Ross.
知道啦，羅斯
Please don't die!
請不要死掉
To get the evaluation before they see it...
我們得在他們看到評估表前 把它拿回來…
we gotta get into Zelner's office. He doesn't get in until 10.
所以我們得溜進查納的辦公室 通常他十點才會到
But his assistant, Betty, comes in early to eat breakfast at her desk.
但他的助理貝蒂一大早 就會到辦公室吃早餐
-That's kind of sad. -Yeah, well, Betty's kind of sad.
-那真的很悲慘 -沒錯，貝蒂有點慘
Which is why I believe I can lure her away with these chocolates.
所以我相信我可以 用這些巧克力把她誘開
While I distract her, you go in.
我誘開她後，你就跑進去
-Got it. -Let's roll.
-我知道了 -我們行動吧
Hello, Rachel. You got a minute?
嗨，瑞秋，你有空嗎？
Yeah, sure, Mr. Zelner. For you? Anything. Minute.
當然，查納先生 你有事嗎？我隨時都有空
Okay, great.
好吧，太棒了
Abort the plan.
取消計劃
Actually, I'd like to speak to both of you.
事實上，我想跟你們兩個談一談
Okay.
好的
Well, can we get you anything,  Mr. Zelner? Maybe some chocolates.
有什麼事需要幫忙嗎？查納先生 或許你想吃點巧克力
No, thanks,  but I'll give these to Betty.
不，謝謝你 但我可以把它們送給貝蒂
So, I read your evaluation of Tag.
我看過你對泰格做的評估表
Or, to use his full name,  Tag "Sweet Cheeks" Jones?
或許我該叫他的全名 泰格「小可愛」瓊斯？
Is something going on with you two?
你們之間有什麼嗎？
Oh, my God,  can you imagine if there was?
我的天啊 你能想像如果有會怎麼樣嗎？
I mean, what would happen exactly?
如果是那樣的話會怎樣？
Well, I'd be forced to file a report.
那樣啊，我一定得寫份報告
I'd have to consult with the legal department.
我得跟法律部門商量
And your future at the company would be in jeopardy.
你們在公司的未來 可能會有問題
-Well.. -Mr. Zelner...
-喔… -查納先生…
I filled in that evaluation.
那份評估表是我寫的
-Oh, no.. -Yeah, yeah.
-喔，不… -對
I thought it would be funny.
我以為這會很好玩
You wrote that you have a cute tushy?
你寫著你有可愛的小屁屁？
Yes.
對
I have a weird sense of humor.
我的幽默感很奇怪
And I'm kind of strangely proud of my butt.
很奇怪地 我以自己的屁股為榮
It's kind of a risky joke, Tag.
開這種玩笑太危險了，泰格
What is this drawing? I can't figure it out.
這到底是在劃什麼？我看不懂
It's upside down, you gotta.. It doesn't matter.
它倒過來了，你得… 那不重要
It's not like I don't have a sense of humor.
我不是沒有幽默感的人
Hell, I even enjoy a naughty limerick every now and then.
沒錯，我甚至很喜歡 寫打油詩
There's a time and a place.
但時間跟地點是很重要的
Unless you have a limerick right now.
除非你有寫打油詩的靈感
No? Okay. Well, you've got my fax number.
沒有嗎？好吧 你知道我的傳真機號碼
I can't believe you did that. That was sweet.
我不敢相信你會那麼做 那太貼心了
-Don't worry about it. -You could've lost your job.
-別擔心 -你可能會丟掉工作
Are you kidding me? With this cute butt, I'd find work.
你在開玩笑嗎？有這麼可愛的屁股 我一定能找到工作
Thank you, you're great.
謝謝你，你太棒了
-You know what? -What?
-你知道嗎？ -什麼？
I feel great.
我感覺棒極了
In fact...
事實上…
What?
什麼？
It's just.. It took me so long to get that desk organized.
我只是…我花了很多時間 才把桌子整理好
I'm sorry.
對不起
There it is.
這就對了
What is going on?
怎麼了？
We're waiting for the candy. Bring out the candy!
我們在等糖果 把糖果拿出來
Yeah, lady, give us candy.
對，小姐，快給我們糖果
Joey!
喬伊
-What's up, buddy? -What are you doing?
-什麼事？兄弟 -你在做什麼？
Waiting to get candy.
我在等著拿糖果
Get in here.
快進來
Hey, and you cannot smoke in here.
嘿，你不能在這裡抽煙
Merry Christmas.
耶誕快樂
The candy is coming! I need another 15 minutes for it to cool.
糖果做好了，我得讓它 冷卻十五分鐘
All right, everybody, just be quiet. Be quiet! Be quiet! Pipe down!
好了，大伙們，安靜 安靜，請閉嘴
What is the matter with you people?
你們是怎麼了？
This woman was trying to do a nice thing for you.
這個女人在為你們做好事
She was making candy so she could get to know all of you...
她想做糖果 是為了要認識你們
and I'll bet that not one of you can tell me her name.
我敢說你們沒有人 能叫出她的名字
Am I right?
我沒說錯吧？
Candy Lady?
她是糖果小姐？
No, not "Candy Lady."
不，不是「糖果小姐」
If we know it, can we have candy?
知道她的名字就能拿到糖果嗎？
All right, you know what?
好吧，你們知道嗎？
Forget it, you've ruined it.
忘了糖果，你們毀了一切
Go home. You've ruined it.
回家去吧，你們毀了一切
That's all wrong! You guys ruined everything. You ruined it!
那是不對的，你們毀了一切 你們毀了這個機會
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
-謝謝 -別客氣
Did you smoke?
你抽了煙嗎？
No, smokes-a-lot lady blew smoke directly into my mouth.
不，老煙槍婆婆 把煙直接噴入我的嘴巴裡
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
Fine, but it was really scary for a while.
我沒事 但剛剛真的有點可怕
Someone slipped a threatening note under the door!
有人會將恐嚇紙條 塞到門縫下
Oh, yeah. Sorry about that. Mob mentality or whatever.
對了，我很抱歉 我的暴力傾向發作了
I can't believe it. I did it. I rode a bike!
我不敢相信，我辦到了 我會騎腳踏車了
I never thought I'd be able to do that. Thank you.
我從來沒想過我能 這麼做，謝謝你
Oh, hey, don't thank me. Thank yourself.
嘿，別謝我 謝謝你自己
You're the one who faced your fears and ultimately overcame them.
是你面對了自己的恐懼 終於克服了它們
Don't be so corny, Ross. It's not an After School Special.
別說些陳腔濫調的話 這不是輔導課